couponraja.in 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy - Couponraja

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our website terms and conditions that apply to your use of our website) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the Site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the Site will constitute your agreement to any such changes. If you have any questions at all about this policy or the Site, or about how we use and process your personal information, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@couponraja.in or, alternatively, in writing to Couponraja.in

Information We May Collect from You

We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those disclosed in this statement.

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information provided by filling in forms on our site www.couponraja.in . This includes, but is not limited to, information provided at the time of registering for our newsletter, posting discounts and other material or contacting us.

We may keep a record of correspondence when you contact us.

Information collected through surveys that we use for research purposes, although you can choose not to participate in such sureveys.

Web logs of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and other communication data and the resources that you access.

IP Addresses and Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our business users. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns.

We may also obtain information about your usage of the Website by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. These cookies enable us to store information about your preferences and customise our site according to your individual interests, speed up your searches and recognise you when you return to our site.

Couponraja.in may also allow advertisers and other third parties to place cookies onto your computer when you visit this website. The cookies placed by advertisers and other third parties are used to keep track of the web searches you make while visiting this website, as well as your web surfing behaviour on this website and other websites you may visit. That information is used to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other websites, and/or to keep track of your response to each ad.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

Direct Mailings

If you register with Couponaraja.in or sign up for any of our newsletters or alerts, we will send you information about our coupon codes, 'free stuff', or other products and services we feel may interest you. Your e-mail address may also be used to send you information about our other websites that we feel are relevant to your registration on Couponraja.in.

You can sign up to our newsletter through submitting their email address at any of the sign up boxes featured throughout the Website or via our User Registration page. By providing your email address you agree to receive regular newsletter emails from Couponraja.in.

You can sign up to our newsletter through submitting their email address at any of the sign up boxes featured throughout the Website or via our User Registration page. By providing your email address you agree to receive regular newsletter emails from Couponraja.in.

Where We Store Your Personal Data

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Updating/Removing Personal Information

It is your responsibility to advise us of the required amendments to your personal details.

If you no longer desire our service, please let us know and we shall correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us. An archive copy of any information provided to us may be retained by us for our records and for audit purposes.

Uses Made of the Information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our affiliate advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users.

Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

We may share information submitted as part of third party promotional activities only when you agree the specific Terms and Conditions of the promotion by opting in to the promotion.

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
